[Music]
chop
down not enough I've beening since the
day I was born stop lying I took a day
off but I started rapping
second pretty great huh I figured we'd
just throw a big sale on all our Asian
stuff on December 7th wow it's racist I
would never not serve an Asian please W
your hands around that corner what's up
yeah
I want to know what love
[Music]
is how was the game oh how was it 11 RBI
10 strikeouts 13 beers that is a Delco
triple double wait a minute you know
that troops thing is tonight right yeah
oh yeah here you go already took care of
it prow so you got nothing left to do
what's this Heroes and ho party you've
endured dday now enjoy double D-Day Tom
this isn't real right oh it is now that
girl I've been seeing from anthropology
she's bringing all of her Coachella
friends to hang out you know the ones
that already have HPV so they're not
afraid it courage courage triple hard
how many girls have you given courage
to okay that's fair well guess what when
you even s a little Chuck-E-Cheese party
I've been making sure that this place is
going to be filled to the brim with hot
ass hot the kind of hot ass that's going
to get these veterans rubbing rifles not
together but separately they're going to
be rubbing the rifles they going to be
rubbing the rif I've had my rifle on
safety for 20
years if you'll excuse me I'm going to
take a power KN I just dropped an adab
it and you can wake me up when this
place smells like gunpowder and
wait you took an adance you're thing is
cucumber Netflix is
1545 and we
[Music]
lost I'm not saying getting shot with a
paintball gun is the same
thing but it
stinks
hey buddy oh hey dude how's it going it
worked yeah it worked look at this look
at this this one this that's Stephanie I
don't give a she's a hot Pearl
Harbor nurse yeah real and this one uh
you know it's just hot and then this one
is like hot Rambo hey how are you I
think this one forgot to uh dress up
well no real nurses can be sexy
too we're playing salute and shoot oh
Troth
[Music]
TR the are you doing I got to wash
both pant legs my arm is asleep here get
it up get it up come here
boy this works dude it's not working
John it's not working stop it
you're going to scare these girls away
I'm going to you up for that the
whole point of this party is to salute
the troops that's the reason we're here
all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right fix it
I'll fix it hold on are you a real nurse
shut up I slept on it I can't
[Music]
salute I got an idea is you think I'm
I'm thinking down here we go fastest
part of the RAC trck yeah definitely oh
my
God what is your email all right this
going to work all right yeah okay trust
me I trust you all
right
how's the look is perfect F yeah Johnny
I knew it thanks all for coming out I'm
Russ Harvey you may know me from Potter
Lumber uh family business you married
in um it it's amazing getting to honor
These Fine veterans you chop down the
enemy allowing us to chop down our
prices on all lighting fixtures and
windows now through
Thursday h i along with my employees of
Potter Lumber would like to thank you
Veterans for your
support um I I just want to say that I
do not support our imperialist uh
foreign
policy here we go here we go here we
go your arm is so heavy keep it up and
to St keep it up it's to
St
what are you doing hey that guy's not
saluting salute the truth Tomy I'm
trying to salute the troops he's jerking
off with the
flag salute the truth Tom jerk I'm
trying to that
nurse stop jerking I'm not I'm not
jerking I'll s with my
[Applause]
left I'd rather you jerk your dick with
your right hand salute with your
[Applause]
left checking off I'm not checking off
I'm not cheing
off well I certainly hope
not sweetheart why don't you go on my
grandfather is the
bravest strongest man I've ever met
it
works what
works D sit
down as fast
as
canun as fast as
[Music]
man